Kettle and Idol
I'd like to go to the main project of Kettle and Idol!
Now please give a cute title call!
My 3 main elements
Am I good?
I'm good? Cute!
Okay, now we are going to ask you to introduce the three elements that make up who you are.
So, please tell us about your three elements. Here is your sketchbook.
Ta-da!
Here it is!
In front of your fans
First, second
School, the third one.
Don't move!
I kind of understand "in front of the fans".
And school...
I kind of get it.
Actually, I'm not sure yet.
I love being in front of my fans.
For example, there are live streaming shows, right?
For example, there are live shows that are streamed to the public because of the Corona Disaster,
But that is not enough for me,
What makes me shine the brightest is when I am standing in front of my fans and doing something in front of them,
I think Akanezora is what it is because of all of you.
I think I get excited in front of the fans,
Have you ever made a mistake because you were too excited?
There have been many times when I got too excited and did something wrong,
When I was performing at Lilie, there was a venue that allowed me to get off the stage,
We decided when to get off the stage. We all decided when to get off the stage.
But I got too excited and got off at a different time on my own,
I was so excited that I got off at a different time on my own, and the members asked me to come back with a microphone.
I think it would be better not to do that, because it would probably startle many staff members.
That's right. I'll be careful.
He suddenly disappeared.
Of course, you do a lot of things like benefit events,
What do you do for newcomers?How do you respond to newcomers?
At the benefit meeting, I say, "Nice to meet you,
If I don't know them well, I introduce myself,
I introduce myself to them and tell them who I am and where I live. I introduce myself to them if I don't know them well, tell them who I am, where I live, etc,
If you're okay with that kind of talk, you can say, "I live in Kanagawa,
I'm in Kanagawa. Like, "Where is your favorite place? Like, "Where is your favorite place?
Yokohama and Chinatown are nice,
I like Yokohama and Chinatown,
And then, "Which group do you often go to? And so on,
I often talk about other groups,
I think we often talk about other groups, and then the conversation moves on.
It's a friendly atmosphere.
I'm totally friendly.
I'm going to be at Ashuan A.'s place for the next few months. I hope you can go to Ashuan A's place for a benefit or something like that,
I hope you can go to Ashuan A.'s place as if you were a friend,
I think it will be easier to get to know you.
It's like this. Always.
By the way, what do you do with people who haven't come to see you in a few years?
I have a very good memory.
I'm very happy with that.
I am really proud of it.
I think I can beat the other members,
I have a very good memory,
I can even tell the names of people who haven't been here in years,
Even if I don't know their name,
I can say, "Hey, I've been here before, right? Even if I don't know their name, I just say, "I've been here before, right?
I am the type of person who can say, "I've been here before," even if they don't know my name, so I get a lot of compliments.
I'm sure that makes the customers happy.
For example, they know where they are sitting,
I understand.
When they come to see me during a live concert, for example,
I can tell if they were on this side of the stage today,
I am the type of person who says, "You were on this side today," or "You were in the front today,
They are surprised that I can see them,
They are surprised that I can see them, but I often tell them that I can see them.
I am surprised that they can see me, but I often tell them that I can see them,I'm glad to hear that you have a good memory,
By the way, do you use it for communication?
Not particularly.
I see.
Kettle? It's been a long time!
You used to come here a lot in the first year, didn't you?
It's been a long time!
Then, it's been about 8 years.
I'm glad to see you're doing well.
Thank you very much. Please come again. Thank you.
Kankan's idol
Mr. Yakan's idol
Did you notice anything at school?
School?
That class? I didn't like that teacher.
There were a lot of things like that.
What about this program?
Akii-san
Mr. Ichu
Mr. Uu
Grandpa
Mirkii-san
Thank you again!
Thank you again for the second time!